Jadelyn Libios

18115 Longmoor Dr. Houston, TX 77084 | 832-334-1790 | jaylibios@gmail.com | Website: https://jadelynlibios.com

Summary

Ambitious and dedicated college student working towards a Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems at the University of Houston. Focused on utilizing my resources to expand my computer programming skills and gain hands-on experience.

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON (HOUSTON, TX)

DEC 2020

· Related coursework: Internet Application Development, Computer Organization and Architecture, Intro to Programming – C++, Intro to Programming II – Java, Information Systems Application Development, Web Design

Work Experience

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT JACK J. VALENTI SCHOOL OF COMMUNICATIONS (UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON)

FEB 2018 - PRESENT

- · Process confidential student documents
- · Interacted with office officials to improve office efficiency by 20% with new file and organization system
- · Trained 2 new administrative assistants
- · Planned and coordinated 3 department teamwork activities

SALES ASSOCIATE BOXLUNCH (HOUSTON, TX)

MAY 2017 - FEB 2018

- · Stocked, replenished, and organized inventory accurately and efficiently
- · Achieved more than 100% of sales goals for 3 consecutive months
- · Supplied outstanding customer service to an average of 40 customers per day
- · Provided support for other team members as necessary with cash handling, suggestive selling, and cleaning

Technical Skills

 Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ReactJS, Java, PHP, SOL · Microsoft Office: Access, Excel, Word

· Adobe: Illustrator, Photoshop, XD

Organizations/Activities

SIGMA KAPPA, LAMBDA DELTA CHAPTER VICE PRESIDENT OF SCHOLARSHIP, 2017

SEPT 2016 - PRESENT

Led other executive members to promote important curriculars and offer 73 women resources and workshops. Developed new system for tracking member study hours, increasing chapter GPA by 0.7 points.

CS GIRLS MEMBER SEPT 2016 - PRESENT

Meet to boost programming knowledge and create female role models able to discuss technical matters and problems; Tour at least 3 companies a semester.

ASSOCIATION OF IT PROFESSIONALS (AITP) MEMBER

IAN 2018 - DEC 2018

Guide members to build professionalism and network with fellow IT professionals from the Houston area; Arranges at least 4 information sessions per month with various tech companies.